ace
高手
look at me with that word I became a gaze trainer I'm the mom and they go
用这个词看着我，我成为了凝视教练。我是妈妈，他们走了
15-year-old Ivan has autism, does not speak and is
15岁的伊万患有自闭症，不会说话，并且是
communicates through an ipad where his entire universe of words and images is
通过ipad进行交流，他的整个单词和图像空间都在其中
I received his diagnosis when I was two and a half years old and I still remember today
我两岁半时得到了她的诊断，今天我仍然记得
that moment with a lot of pain with my husband we felt very lost
那一刻，我丈夫非常痛苦，我们感到非常失落
we did not know where to start there was no internet as now you could not
我们不知道从哪里开始，没有互联网，因为现在您无法
ignore information so these first steps were pure intuition
忽略信息，所以这些第一步纯属直觉
iván did not hold the gaze he had lost the words he said no
伊万没有凝视，他失去了他说不的话
answered their name and nothing we did to them as if the words were
回答了他们的名字，我们没有对他们做任何事情，好像这些话是
noises
杂音
the only way I had to know what was wrong with him what he felt was
我唯一要知道他出了什么问题的唯一方法就是
looking into his eyes
看着他的眼睛
that bridge was rock like showing him the villalba when he shared things that
那座桥是岩石，就像他分享一些东西时向他展示Villalba
they liked així I did not look and we were together like this
他们喜欢我没看过的艾克斯，我们在一起就像这样
that I dedicated myself to follow him in those things so that every time he unit more and more
我全心全意地跟随他在这些事情上，以便每次他团结起来的时候越来越多
moments of gazes we spend hours and hours when he stains her with her sister
当他凝视着她的妹妹时，我们花了数小时的时间
Major Alexia and in this round of Haiti is
亚历克西娅少校和本轮海地是
rag was looking for me there at that moment I felt that I was
那一刻，抹布在那儿找我，我觉得我在
river we also have a record now in the pool he always had a very passionate
河里，我们现在在游泳池里也有记录，他一直都很热情
strong because of the water I remember that I was two and a half years old and
因为水而坚强，我记得我已经两岁半了，
one winter day with lots of rain I was carrying a covered pool
一个冬天有很多雨，我提着一个有盖的游泳池
because even those days we were not there we were going down the highway and
因为即使那些日子我们不在那儿，我们也要沿着高速公路走，
I made the wrong exit and there she started crying inconsolably without stopping until
我走错了出口，在那里她开始哭得很伤心，没有停下来，直到
that I get back on the road and just then it calmed down, how was it possible that with two years
我回到路上，然后才平静下来，两年后怎么可能
and a half did not respond to its name but in the middle of this rain it is flour that
有一半没有回应它的名字，但是在下雨的时候是面粉
he could not see anything he was able to perfectly recognize the path
他看不到任何东西，他完全能够认出这条路
there I realized that they will have an exceptional visual memory and that this
在那里，我意识到他们将拥有非凡的视觉记忆，这
I was going to pass and the front door so I started taking pictures of everything and
我正要经过前门，所以我开始为所有东西拍照
teaching him life continues to be shown from photo to photo and still today is
教他一生的生活仍在不断地从照片中展现出来，而今天仍然是
the way they went tells us what he wants is what he needs and
他们走的路告诉我们他想要的就是他的需要，
also what he always is but not only was the rival look
他一直都是，但不仅是对手的样子
[Music] was also the lives of others
[音乐]也是别人的生命
how to achieve that they not only look at the auc and added but that they look at him with
如何实现他们不仅看了auc和添加，而且他们看了他
all that he can give with all that he is capable of chance with the things that
他所能给予的一切，以及他有能力与之相处的机会
they like the ones that don't like any of us but for that I also had
他们喜欢那些不喜欢我们的人，但为此我也有
what to do on my part I had to encourage myself to let go and it cost me
我该怎么做，我不得不鼓励自己放手，这让我付出了代价
very much
非常
iván was 11 years old and this is a treatment very close to
iván是11岁，这是一个非常接近的治疗
home in another neighborhood and one afternoon while
在另一个街区和一个下午的房子里
I had been waiting for him for a long time at a greengrocery store in the neighborhood that
我在附近的一家杂货店里等了很久
He has a bit of everything and between purchases he likes to chat with josé g
他拥有一切，在两次购买之间，他喜欢和何塞·格聊天
Contra iván's owner who had autism and that I wanted him to take care of her
Contraiván患有自闭症的主人，我想让他照顾她
to walk alone down the street without anyone being the hand and I was encouraged to
独自一人走在街上，没有人牵着手，我受到鼓舞
ask him if the garlic games the afternoon were going could he come to help the
问他下午是否要参加大蒜比赛，他可以来帮忙吗
order from the water bottle shelves because she loved to order and prize
从水壶架上订购，因为她喜欢订购并获得奖品
buy some chocolate cookies his favorite recipes
买一些他最喜欢的食谱的巧克力饼干
He immediately said yes and that's how it was for a year
他立即说是的，这就是一年的样子
iván would come to josé's greengrocer, help him to see the shelves of bottles
iván来找josé的蔬菜商，帮助他看瓶子的架子
of water that were left with the labels perfectly enchiladas
带有标签的水完美地玉米饼馅
millimetrically to the same side and left happy with his cookies from
千里走到同一边，对他的曲奇感到满意
chocolate plus josé is not an expert on autism you don't have to be an expert on
Chocolate plusjosé不是自闭症专家，您不必是自闭症专家
nothing and be no feat to include out
什么也没有，包括在内的壮举
we just have to be
我们只需要
more
更多的
well it is no fault
好吧，这不是错
we just have to be close
我们只需要靠近
If something scares us or we don't understand it, let's ask, let's be curious, but never
如果有什么让我们感到害怕或我们不明白，那就问一下，让我们感到好奇，但永远不要
indifferent let us have the courage to look into each other's eyes because with our
冷漠让我们有勇气看着对方的眼睛，因为有了我们
look we can open a world to another fact
看起来我们可以为另一个事实打开世界